Amelia Goodson

Web Developer

Inquisitive and driven web developer with a flair for design and thirst for knowledge. Experienced in working with teams to produce digital content that engages customers and delivers conversions. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React, I enjoy creating functional, accessible and responsive websites from the initial wireframing to deployment.

Professional Experience

Communications & Policy Assistant, Landcom

Sydney (February 2018 – January 2022) Responsibilities:

- Maintained corporate website using WordPress content management system and associated plugins.
- Organised large-scale conference of government leaders, including venues, designing the agenda and theme, soliciting speakers and making travel arrangements.
- Verified factual content of the Annual Report, which involved fact-checking hundreds of statements via research and consultation.
- Wrote compliments and complaints policy and managed the accompanying reporting system, periodically conducting internal training on the policy and process.
- Managed departmental budgets and acted as first point of call for advice on procurement.

Executive Assistant, Corporate Finance, Ashurst

London (December 2015 – September 2017) Responsibilities:

- Performed billable legal work including drafting share pledges, account pledges and facility agreements;
- Drafted submissions to the Board in regards to post-Brexit implications for the business;
- Managed expenses including credit card reconciliation and expense reimbursement; and
- Provided high-level administrative and legal support to four senior associates and one senior partner by amending legal documents, organising travel and managing diaries.

Executive Assistant, Commercial Disputes, Herbert Smith Freehills

Sydney (February 2012 - September 2014) Responsibilities:

- Supported partners and associates in areas of complex commercial litigation and transactions.
- Managed monthly billing of over \$1 million to high-profile clients.
- Prepared case summaries and detailed evidence

Contact

Email

ameliajanegoodson@gmail.com

Portfolio

www.ameliagoodson.com

Skills

UX Design - wireframing and

prototyping

HTML

CSS

Responsive Design

JavaScript

jQuery

React

Node

- chronologies.
- Handled office scheduling and made notes for deadlines, motions and other important dates.
- Completed document revisions, court document filings, travel arrangements and client billing.

Legal Secretary, Workers Compensation, DLA Piper

Sydney (February 2010 - January 2012) Responsibilities:

- Provided paralegal support for one high volume fee-earner, managing over 400 files;
- Reviewed insurance, surveillance and medical reports to assess claims and damages;
- Liaised with clients regarding complex workers compensation matters; and
- Drafted documents including affidavits, depositions, letters of demand and briefs to counsel.

Education

2021-07 - 2021-10	IT Support Professional Certificate
2021 10	Google
2020-01 - 2020-07	Full-Stack Web Development Certificate
,	University Of Sydney & Trilogy
2019-11 - 2020-01	Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing Short Course
2020 02	Google Digital Garage
2017-01 - 2020-06	Bachelor Of Laws (First Class Hons)
2020 00	University Of New England Thesis topic: Examining liability frameworks to accommodate injuries resulting from Al in healthcare.
2013-01 - 2015-10	Diploma Of Business <i>TAFE NSW</i> Award for Most Outstanding Student
2006	Higher School Certificate
	St Mary's Senior High School

UAI score: 98.55. Premier 's Award and Award for Most Outstanding Student